What are the four words that can totally
you in a match? They can put you
in a victim mindset. Everything is
happening to you, you think, and you
believe you have no control over
anything. Have you guessed it? It's here
we go again. Flush that down the toilet
right away. It does zero good for you.
You are not a victim. Take
responsibility for your innings at the
table. One bad roll doesn't mean the end
of the match. Nineball has a 10 to 15%
luck factor into it. That's the name of
the game. Accept that and try to have as
many quality shots around one or two
freaky shots in a match. That's your
process goal. Work the process of what
you need to do in order to execute good
shots and flush all the other stuff.
Here we go again. All you need to do is
cross out that one word again and you're
left with here we go. Go for it. Good
luck. [snorts]